# **Gumenniy Andrey**

Adress: Poligonna street, Dnipro

**Phone:** 0957834871

Email: gumenniy.andrew@gmail.com

Current Job: Front End Developer, Imagineer Technology Group



#### **About**

7 years in IT industry, about 2 years in Front End Development (current experience) and 5 years in knowledge management (corporate knowledge base). Worked with Angular 2+, RESTful API, Bootstrap 4. Experience in third-party libraries integration - DevExtreme (controls, grids, charts), angular plugins.

# **Work Experience**

11.2018 - Present (2 years)

# Front End Developer (Angular 2+) / Imagineer Technology Group (Fintech)

- writing client-side logic for CRM system (Angular 8);
- third party libraries integration (DevExtreme, PrimeNG);
- working with REST API;
- HTML coding (bootstrap 4);

10.2013 - 03.2018 (5 years)

# **Knowledge Base Specialist / Noosphere, Administrative department**

- HTML/CSS coding of individual pages
- Writing technical documentation
- Data collection, analysis and publishing in the internal wiki-storage
- Promotion of internal resources of the company (internal mailings, using HTML template and writing internal news)

10.2011 - 03.2013 (1,5 years)

# **Engineer - researcher / United Engineering Company**

- Writing technical documentation
- Statistical analysis of measurement results
- Non-destructive testing of finished products

#### **Skills**

### **Programming languages**

- Javascript (2,5 years experience)
- HTML / CSS3 (3 years experience)
- C# (1 year experience) Basic

#### **Frameworks**

- Angular 2-8 (2,5 years experience)
- Bootstrap 4 (2,5 years experience)

#### JavaScript libraries

- jQuery (1,5 years experience)
- RxJS (2,5 years experince)
- DevExtreme (controls, grids, charts) (2 years experience)
- PrimeNG (2 years experience)
- Highcharts (4 months experince)

#### **Programs and tools**

- Git (2 years experience)
- Visual Studio Code, Visual Studio IDE (2 years experience)

#### English level - pre-intermediate

#### Education

#### **Dnepropetrovsk National University**

2007-2012

Devices and systems of nondestructive testing / Master Degree

### **Web Development Courses**

#### **Online learning**

- Angular 6 The Complete Guide / Udemy
- Angular & NodeJS The MEAN Stack Guide / Udemy
- Build an app with ASPNET Core and Angular from scratch / Udemy
- Official Guide Angular
- HTML Academy
- W3Schools Online Web Tutorials
- Learn JavaScript

09.2015 - 03.2016

# **Computer School Hillel**

(5 months)

"Front-end course" (in-depth course about front-end)

- HTML 5 / CSS3, Bootstrap
- Basics of javascript
- HTTP and AJAX
- OOP in Javascript
- jQuery
- AngularJS

03. 2015 - 06.2015

#### World ORT (Dnipro)

(3 months)

The course "Fundamentals of Web Development" (review course: frontend and back-end)

#### References

**GitHub** - https://github.com/AndrewGumenniy

**Portfolio -** https://andrewgumenniy.github.io/portfolio/

Facebook - https://www.facebook.com/gymennui

**Linkedin -** https://www.linkedin.com/in/andrey-gumenniy-5258a680/